迈克! 迈克! 迈克!
Mike! Mike! Mike!
国会票选平局次日晨
距参议院投票还有1天
上午 9:02
总统会对国会投票这一事
Mike, will the president
发表声明吗?
be making a statement about the House vote?
不 总统现在不会对此事发表声明
No, the president will not be making a statement at this time.
即使她对结果表示失望
While she was disappointed in the result,
她仍然很欣慰我国有如此健全有力的民主选举
she was thrilled to watch democracy in action.
这种事在俄罗斯可不会发生
I mean, the chances of this happening in Russia, nyet.
如果汤姆·詹姆斯胜过蒙特兹议员
Mike, if Tom James wins against Senator Montez
成为了总统的话
in the Senate and becomes president,
总统梅耶会考虑...
will President Meyer consider...
我得打断你
Okay, let me cut you off right there.
赛琳娜·梅耶不会考虑再做副总统
Selina Meyer is not interested in becoming vice president again.
这份职务不在她的考虑范围之内
That job is in her rearview mirror.
我以我的名声起誓
I stake my reputation on this.
赛琳娜·梅耶永远不会再做副总统
Selina Meyer will never be vice president ever, ever again.
汤姆 直说吧
So, Tom, let's be real.
汤姆 詹姆斯办公室
距参议员投票还有1天
上午 9:23
你很可能成为意外总统[副总统因总统遭弹劾/辞职/死亡而接替总统]
You're gonna be an accidental president.
秃子笑和尚[瑟琳娜也是意外总统]
Pot, kettle.
为了尽可能顺利地
I'm here to offer my help
度过这个权利转换的过程
in making this transition of power
我来贡献我自己的力量
as smooth as possible
加入你的内阁
by joining your administration.
奇怪啊 我也这么想
Well, strangely enough, I was thinking along the same lines.
太棒了 我告诉你我要什么
Okay, fantastic. I'll tell you what I want.
国务卿
I want secretary of state
至少这样吧
'cause I think that's the least you can do.
我想的是副总统
I was thinking vice president.
这真的是最低要求了
That's literally the least you can do.
我就想要国务卿
And I really want secretary of state.
- 副总统 - 就国务卿吧
- Vice president. - Come on, secretary of state.
副总统赛琳娜·梅耶多耳熟能详啊
Vice President Meyer's got a nice familiar ring to it.
才没有
No, it doesn't.
副总统 不要就算了
Vice president, take it or leave it.
就算是你就职典礼前面的山坡上
I wouldn't be your veep if there were a grassy knoll
长满像朱迪·福斯特粉丝一样的杀手小天使
full of Jodie Foster fans in the front row
朱迪 福斯特一粉丝曾试图刺杀里根总统以取得偶像注意
我都不会做你副总统
at your inauguration.
那就算了
That's a leave it.
我宁愿让乔治·华盛顿从墓里爬出来
General George Washington could climb
我每天舔他烂掉的木头屁眼两次
out of his grave right now and I would rather eat out
也不愿意做汤姆的狗屁副总统
his zombified wooden asshole twice a day
什么狗屁位置我都不要
than be his vice fucking-- fucking anything!
那副总统这条路就先放放
Okay, let's put a pin in the VP for now.
- 逗我呢? - 早上好 女士
- Seriously? - Morning, ma'am.
叫醒迈克 或者算了 反正醒不醒都一样
Will somebody wake up Mike? Or not. What's the difference?
女士 昨晚我做了一个总统政绩的统计
Ma'am, last night I ran a flash poll on presidential scholars.
你被评为第四十三位最杰出的总统
They have rated you the 43rd most effective president ever.
- 总共有多少位? - 四十四
- Out of how many? - Kent: 44.
您排在詹姆斯·布坎南前面
You were right ahead of James Buchanan,
他因引发了内战受人诟病
who many feel caused the Civil War.
肯特 下次你决定从菊花进来的时候
Kent, can you give a girl some warning next time
给人家个提醒先吧?
before you jam it in the back door?
数据不做提醒的 女士
Data gives no warning, ma'am.
马乔里和凯瑟琳有可能结婚吗?
Any chance Marjorie and Catherine want to get married?
看吧 第一场白宫女同性恋婚礼
There you go, first White House lesbian wedding.
这会让你载入史册的
That'll get you in the history books.
我受不了木吉他的声音了[偏见认为蕾丝边大多弹吉他]
Oh, God. I can't take that much acoustic guitar.
我们还是要
What we have to do
解放西藏
is we have to make Tibet happen.
这才能成就我的辉煌
That's what's gonna be my legacy.
赛琳娜·梅耶 解放了西藏的女人
Selina Meyer, the woman who freed Tibet.
女士 我们已经两个星期
Ma'am, we've been in radio
没有和中方进行通话了
silence with the Chinese for the last two weeks.
我们干嘛不能直接
Well, then why don't we
塞几艘战舰到中国南边那堆海里去?
send warships out into the South China Seas?
- 就叫南海 - 我要我的诺贝尔和平奖!
- Sea. - I want my Nobel Peace Prize!
我的辉煌!
Legacy!
辉煌的会议结束了
Legacy meeting adjourned.
上帝 我的电话要被电视台的邀约给撑炸了
God, my phone is blowing up with these TV offers.
我觉得我需要一个经纪人
Think I'm gonna need an agent, you know,
重新打造一个更加高端的丹·伊根品牌
someone who can take the Dan Egan brand to the next level.
戈培尔自杀了真是可惜[纳粹德国宣传部长]
Too bad Goebbels killed himself.
我是从罗斯福以来
The only president
第二个坐着小编的总统[罗斯福长期依赖轮椅]
to pee sitting down since FDR.
这他妈就算我最大的业绩了 是不是
Is that gonna be my legacy, Ben? Is it?
我尿多的时候也坐着小便
Well, I pee sitting down sometimes if it's gonna be a longy.
我们必须要把西藏这事搞定
Okay, we've got to make Tibet happen.
通过卡塔尔人去协商 好吗?
Go through the Qataris, okay?
我相信现在肯定有一堆卡塔尔人
I bet there are a dozen of
在乔治城的四季酒店里
them right now at the Georgetown Four Seasons.
或者去兰博基尼店里找找
Go to a Lamborghini dealership, you know?
或者有妓女的地方找 这些人估计知道路子
Wherever they have prostitutes. These guys could help you.
你的牛逼光荣榜我弄完了
I'm finished with your brag wall.
你和华盛顿精英们的合照都在这了
All the photos of you with the Washington elite.
有没有总统不吼我的
Are there any pictures where the president isn't yelling at me?
我估计全宇宙
As far as I can tell,
都找不出一张了
no such picture exists in the known universe.
我们得招进来几个养眼的
Oh, also, we got to get some eye candy in here.
雇几个性感实习生
You know, hire some hot interns.
杰夫舅舅从新罕布什尔送来了一堆简历
Oh, Uncle Jeff sent a bunch of resumes from New Hampshire.
有一个是一张酒吧餐巾纸上写着个号码
One of them was a phone number on a bar napkin.
不 新罕布什尔州都是那种
No, New Hampshire is just a fancy word for "It's cold outside,
- "外边冷 所以我没刮阴毛"的女人 - 我记下来了
- so I don't shave my pubes." - I'm writing that down.
- 重点从天气暖和的州招人好吗? - 议员先生...
- Focus on the warm-weather states, okay? - Congressman...
我有种预感 你将要成就一番伟业
I have a feeling you're gonna do some really great things.
我有点饿了 你能马上找个说客
I'm getting kind of hungry. Do you think you could find
请我吃个午饭吗?
a lobbyist to take me out to lunch short notice?
找大型制药公司 他们建了棕榈岛度假中心
Try for Big Pharma. I hear they do The Palm.
总统女士 不得不说
Madam President, I'm afraid to tell you
与阿里 贾法尔大使会面
参议院投票日
上午 8:37
现在您已不再掌权
that the Chinese are rather nervous about moving forward
恐怕中国人无意进一步与您就西藏问题进行洽谈
with Tibet now that you're out of power.
我没有不掌权... 根本没有
I am not out of power and... at all.
还没有正式宣布
This has not, in fact, been formally announced yet,
但我会继续在职...
but I will be continuing on...
...作为
...as
作为副总统
as vice president.
汤姆·詹姆斯昨天提供的职位
Tom James offered it yesterday.
其实更像是并列总统
It's really more of a copresident position.
- 是不是 本? - 当然
- Wouldn't you agree with that, Ben? - Sure.
而且只跟你一个人讲
And between you and me,
汤姆·詹姆斯不太健康
Tom James could be healthier, I have to say.
- 真的? - 是的 他有点 你懂的...
- Oh? - Yeah, he's a bit of a, you know...
我猜这对中国肯定大有益处
Well, I suspect this will be of great interest to the Chinese.
太棒了 非常感谢 谢谢你
Great. Thank you very much. Yes, thank you.
对了 不能碰触女士
Oh, right, no touchy the ladies.
不不 没关系 这是私人事宜
Oh, no, no. It's fine. It's private.
别让我们国家那些疯子知道就行
Just don't let the lunatics back home know.
快点 本 我们走吧
All right, come on, Ben, let's go.
- 好的 女士 - 这简直要完
- Yes, ma'am. - This is gonna suck.
等下 我得先去个地方
Hang on, I need to make a stop.
- 总统女士 - 副总统在里面吗?
- Madam President. - Is the vice president in?
不 他在参议院投票
No, he's at the Senate for the vote.
好吧 我可以的
Okay, I can do this.
- 赛琳娜·梅耶 见到你真愉快 - 汤姆
- Selina Meyer. What a delight. - Tom.
我有好消息
Um, I've got good news.
- 我已经决定... - 别 别说
- I have decided to... - No, don't tell me.
你已经决定分毫不剩地
You have decided to throw away
抛弃所有的尊严
every last shred of dignity you have
接受我给你的副总统一职吗?
and accept my offer of the vice presidency.
我... 我想是的 没错
I... I guess so, yeah.
听你这样说 我很高兴
I'm delighted to hear it.
- 谢谢 - 别担心
- Thank you. - I don't want you to worry.
你可不会是个普普通通的副总统
You are not just gonna be any vice president.
你将成为我的搭档...
You're gonna be a partner...
还是我内阁中不可或缺的一份子
and a very important part of my administration.
- 我操你妈的 - 不 我讲正经的
- You're a motherfucker. - No, I'm serious. I'm serious.
你将成为... 你会是我们团队的一份子
You're gonna be... you know, you're gonna be part of the team.
- 你有资格出席每一场会议 - 好的
- You're gonna be at every meeting. - Okay.
这就像是一个晦气的土拨鼠日
It's like a shitty Groundhog Day.
国家对你感激不尽
Your country thanks you.
国会议员 乔纳 瑞安办公室
雷伯恩大楼 新罕布什尔州
瑞安国会议员办公室
Congressman Ryan's office.
- 瑞安国会议员办公室 - 你好
- Congressman Ryan's office. - Hello.
- 先生 早上好 - 早上好
- Morning, sir. - Morning.
- 早上好 先生 - 瑞安国会议员办公室
- Morning, sir. - Congressman Ryan's office.
理查德 这些是谁?
Richard, who are these dudes?
- 新的实习生 - 什么?
- Oh, these are the new interns. - What?
那是柯尔特 弗吉尼亚大学毕业 玩过长曲棍球
That's Colt. He's from UVA. Played lacrosse.
理查德 我让你招的是性感实习生
Richard, I told you to get hot interns.
先生 根据客观标准
Sir, by any objective standards,
柯尔特 布兰德和梅森都超级性感 无可非议啊
Colt, Brady, and Mason are unequivocally hot, not not.
性感实习生是指妹子 你他妈怎能能不懂这个?
Hot interns means girls. How the fuck do you not know that?
先生 打扰一下 给您冲了一杯拿铁
Excuse me, sir. I made you a latte.
谢谢
Uh, thank you.
这咖啡简直太赞了
Mmm, oh, my God, this coffee is exceptional.
谢谢
Thanks.
- 我们能留下他吗? - 当然可以
- Can we please keep him? - Yeah, absolutely.
嗨 柯尔特 欢迎加入瑞安团队
Hey, Colt, welcome to team Ryan.
我希望你们习惯两件事
I want you guys to get used to two things...
白天在国会山奋勇厮杀
killing it daily on the Hill
晚上还能精液四射
and nights rated PG-squirteen.
- 钱妹两不误 - 钱妹两不误
- Baller. - Baller.
副总统选举马上就要开始了
We are moments away from the Senate vote
参议院将在
for vice president between
汤姆·詹姆斯和劳拉·蒙特兹议员之间做出选择
Senator Tom James and Senator Laura Montez.
詹姆斯VS蒙特兹 历史性的投票
当然 由于总统一职空缺
And, of course, with the presidency vacant,
投票胜出的一方将成为总统
the winner of this vote will assume the presidency.
陆主席 我很欣慰
Well, President Lu, I'm very glad
我们能够达成一致
that we've come to an agreement
我也对于能够在接下来的
and I'm exceptionally glad
四年里继续与您合作感到十分高兴
that we're gonna have another four years of working together.
能够同詹姆斯议员共事
President Lu is particularly
陆主席也非常高兴
happy to work alongside Senator James.
他听说他是个真正的政治家
He hears he's quite the statesman.
他凑合吧 当然这只是个玩笑
Statesman-ish, which is a joke, of course.
- 女士? - 怎么了?
- Ma'am? - What?
得去看看参议院的情况了
We've got to see what's going on in the Senate right away.
你逗我吧
You're kidding.
不好意思 陆主席
Forgive me, President Lu,
恐怕我得离开去参加
but I'm afraid I have to go and attend to
我国参议院正在进行的选举了
the vote that is happening right now in our Senate.
您可以在电视上
But feel free to follow along on the television
或通过你们安插在白宫各个角落里的
or perhaps on one of the many bugs
某个窃听器上收看 请自便
that you've planted throughout the White House.
- 洛厄尔先生 - 詹姆斯议员
- Mr. Lowell. - Senator James.
詹姆斯
蒙特兹
我们情况怎么样?
Jesus Christ. What have we got?
形势比我们想的严峻 女士 汤姆才领先了两票
It's tighter than we thought, ma'am. Tom up by two.
- 什么? - 默里先生
- What? - Mr. Murray.
- 蒙特兹议员 - 一票了
- Senator Montez. - Up by one.
- 汤姆 这是怎么了? - 我不知道 我...
- Tom, what's going on in here? - I don't know, I...
蒙特兹议员
Senator Montez.
- 操你妈的! - 纳尔逊没投给你?
- You motherfucker! - Nelson voted against you?
但纳尔逊是你的骨灰级支持者啊 伙计
But Nelson is your protamine, man.
快打电话给纳尔逊...
Get Nelson on the phone right...
- 这不可能啊 - 汤姆 他已经投过了
- this doesn't just happen. - Tom, he voted!
他们按名字顺序来的 找个排他后面的
They're going alphabetically. Get somebody after him.
- 快电话联系华莱士 - 联系华莱士!
- Get Wallace on the phone. - Get Wallace!
外面在传你水军诋毁门
I'm hearing something about your "Borking" Dunkirk.
- 啥? - 那个在巡回法院被提名的人
- What? - Yeah, on a circuit court nominee.
那都是... 那都是十年前的事了
That was... no. That was 10 years ago.
有人在搞我
Someone is trying to fuck me.
我投给汤姆·詹姆斯
Tom James.
萨默林 你这小便失禁的老家伙 太谢谢了
Thank you, Summerlin, you senile old piss sponge.
- 50比48了 - 再有一票就赢了
- 50-48. - Tom needs just one more.
现在各种关于选票交易的谣言满天飞啊
Got all kinds of rumors about vote trading.
- 又不是我们交易的 - 妈的 华莱士要投给蒙特兹了
- It's not us. - Oh, fuck. Wallace is going Montez.
她到处跟别人说
She's telling people that
你拒绝了她净化阿拉斯加海岸的提案
you reneged on her Alaskan coast cleanup bill.
我是在拉拢石油大亨啊
That was a handout to Big Oil.
根据宪法第七修正案票选副总统
詹姆斯
蒙特兹
总票数
- 华莱士夫人 - 我投给蒙特兹议员
- Mrs. Wallace. - Senator Montez.
50比49 蒙特兹肯定有帮手
50-49. This is not Montez. She's getting help.
- 尤里先生 - 给点力啊 你这个夏威夷墙头草死胖子
- Mr. Yinui. - Come on, you page-diddling Hawaiian fat fuck.
根据宪法第七修正案票选副总统
詹姆斯
蒙特兹
总票数
我投给蒙特兹议员
Senator Montez.
- 50比50了 - 又平局了不要啊
- That's 50. - Not another tie.
- 所以现在是怎样? - 参议院表决平局
- What now? - A tie in the Senate
则参议院议长获得投票权
is broken by the president of the Senate.
也就是副总统
Or what we humans call the vice president.
太好了 你可以投给你自己 快去啊
Oh, my God, perfect. You can vote for yourself. Go, go, go, go.
- 汤姆不是副总统 总管大人 - 道尔才是
- Tom's not veep, you butler. - Doyle is vice president.
获得投票权
Being called upon to cast this vote
是我的荣幸 这是一个光荣的任务
is a pleasure and an honor,
绝不是个负担
not a burden.
我们的国家已经经历了太多的不确定
There's been enough uncertainty in this country,
所以我不会再拖延
so I won't stall any further.
根据宪法第七修正案票选副总统
詹姆斯
蒙特兹
总票数
- 拜托 - 你丫的 有屁快放
- Please. - Come on, just spit it out.
我谨记这些 所以我投给劳拉·蒙特兹
With this in mind, I vote for Senator Laura Montez.
现已正式确定
It's official.
美利坚合众国将迎来新一任总统
The United States of America has a new president.
对劳拉·蒙特兹来说
This is a truly stunning turn of events
这真是个极大的反转
for Laura Montez.
现在你知道我的感受了
Now you know what it feels like.
我收到个消息 是道尔策划了这整件事
I've got a source. Apparently Doyle masterminded the whole thing.
- 有谣言说他被许诺了国务卿的位置  - 国务卿
- Rumor has it he's getting secretary of state. - Secretary of state.
天啊 我恨这个国家
God, I hate this country.
我懂
I know.
你们这群狗日的
You fuckers.
胆子太大了
How dare you?
那个伟大的女人
That magnificent woman
对你们期望那么大 你们却让她失望了
counted on you and you losers let her down.
我得挂了 有好戏看
Yeah, I got to call you back. Something amazing is happening.
你们这些傻逼他妈的就只在乎你们自己
All you fucking cared about was your stupid, bad selves.
你那些数据... 那些数据就是垃圾
Your numbers... your numbers are garbage.
你那些演讲稿 也是垃圾
Your speeches, garbage.
还有你 你应该给她好的建议
And you're supposed to give her advice?
对吧? 你的建议又蠢又傻
Is that right? All I heard was dumb,
我都不知道是些什么
stupid I don't know what the fuck it was.
是垃圾?
Garbage?
- 盖瑞... - 闭嘴吧你!
- Gary... - Oh, shut up!
你从各方面[各种体位]
You screwed her the worst.
搞她搞得最厉害
In all the ways.
是的 我知道...
Oh, I know...
我知道你们嘲笑我
I know you make fun of me
我知道你们觉得我很滑稽
and I know that you think that I'm funny
我是很滑稽 哈哈哈 但至少我在乎她
and I'm funny, ha, ha, ha. Well, at least I cared.
我做好了我的工作 我他妈的在乎!
I did my job! I fucking cared!
能看到这一出 这一年的辛苦也值了
Well, that just kind of made this whole year worth it.
同意
Yeah.
今天是对民主主义意义重大的一天
Today is a great day for democracy.
标志着美国崭新未来的开启
It marks the beginning of a new chapter for America.
新当选总统蒙特兹发表致辞
我们刚刚见证的投票
You know, the vote we
清楚地传递了一个信息
just witnessed sends one very clear message.
此刻起 我们要搁置争议
Now is the time we put our divisions aside
共创美国的美好明天
and we move this great nation forward.
我刚刚跟我的好朋友 比尔·奥布莱恩议员通过话
I just spoke to my good friend Senator Bill O'Brien
我很高兴地宣布
and I'm happy to say
他会全力支持我
he's fully endorsing my presidency,
我会好好利用他的帮助...
so I will be counting on his help...
我想吃水果
I need fruit.
我会带领美国走出这段混乱的时期
as I guide America out of these turbulent times.
国会代表将不会再次投票
十天后
距就职典礼还有1天
这就是她啦 我的宝宝 艾伦
Here she is, baby Ellen.
她看起来真的太大了 不像是个宝宝
Yeah, she seems really, really large for a baby.
我三岁的时候也是个大宝宝
I was a tall kid when I was three.
我们那的邻居
In fact, people in the
都以为我是不是有啥问题
neighborhood thought something was wrong with me
因为我简直是个五岁孩子的个头
cause I was the size of a five-year-old.
所以你到底是哪出了问题呢?
So what's the reason now, then?
早安 总统女士 我回来了
Morning, Madam President. I am back.
- 你之前不在这儿? - 我去了内华达六天
- Were you gone? - Nevada. Six days.
那是段不错的旅程
Yeah, it was a really, really amazing visit.
这是我奶奶的画
This is Mee-Maw's painting back
给我送回家去
here and I want to make sure to get this home.
好的 不过严格来讲 那是凯瑟琳的
Okay, that's technically Catherine's painting.
罗伯特 理查德
文稿代理公司
- 嗨 - 哈喽
- Hey. - Hello.
你也是来推销青年小黄书点子的吗?
Are you here selling a young adult fiction idea, too?
我的讲的是在一个平行宇宙里
Mine takes place in an alternate timeline
那里的肥胖酗酒前总统幕僚长
where overweight, alcoholic ex-chiefs of staff
被人抢着上
are considered a sexual prize.
平行宇宙无非是
Alternate timelines are a crutch
给敷衍的科幻提供个大背景 比如 《星际迷航》
for lazy sci-fi premises, e.G., "Star Trek"
除了《深空九号》
with the exception of "Deep Space Nine."
你该试试写浪漫小说
You should try your hand at romance novels.
- 我试过 - 哦
- I have. - Mmm.
你听说蒙特兹
You hear Montez is looking
想要留下一位高级白宫职员了吗?
to keep one senior White House staffer?
大概就是个谣言吧 不在乎
Probably just a rumor. Wouldn't worry about it.
就职典礼前夜
下午 8:17
按照惯例 总统当选人蒙特兹女士
As is customary, President-Elect Montez
和她的家人今晚将下榻布莱尔大厦
and her family will spend tonight at Blair House.
明早10点 她将在就职典礼前
Tomorrow morning at 10:00 A.M., she will join President Meyer
与梅耶总统在红厅
for coffee in the Red Room
喝咖啡
before heading to the inauguration.
白宫
下午 10:49
MSNBC刚刚获知总统当选人蒙特兹女士
MSNBC has just learned that President-Elect Montez
蒙特兹欲挖查理·贝尔德任财政部长
计划提名华尔街银行家查理·拜尔德...
plans to nominate Wall Street banker Charlie Baird...
果不其然
That seems about right.
为财政部长
to be her secretary of the treasury.
梅耶总统去年年底和这位银行家短暂有染
President Meyer dated the banker briefly late last year.
嘿 理查德
hey, Richard.
总统女士
Madam President.
我在打包收拾议员的旧办公室
I'm just finishing packing up Congressman Ryan's old office.
必须现在做 因为这是最后一晚...
I have to do it now because it's the last night before...
对啊 我知道是什么的最后一晚
Yeah, I know what it's the last night before of.
你知道柯尔特的生日宴会吗
You know about Colt's birthday dinner?
- 这样很好 不是吗 -非常 非常 非常放松
- It's good, isn't it? - It's very, very, very relaxing.
我应该更信赖你 理查德
I should have relied on you more, Richard.
我是说真的 你算是个好员工
I mean, really, seriously, you're one of the good ones.
谢谢 总统女士
thank you, Madam President.
如果我有100个理查德
If I had had 100 Richards,
谁知道我能做成什么呢
who knows what I could have done?
可能会很多
Probably a lot.
也可能最后像《阴阳魔界》里的场景
Or it could turn out like one of those "Twilight Zone" Scenarios
大家彼此谋杀
where we all murder each other.
我都不记得怎么开车了
I don't even remember how to drive.
- 我得买个钱包 - 大概吧
- I need a wallet. - Probably.
- 还有邮票 我要买点邮票 - 对
- And stamps. I've got to get stamps. - Yeah.
如果我是个小女孩 然后你对我说
If I was a little girl and you said to me,
"你想做什么"
"What do you want to do?"
我可能会说"可以让我做总统吗"
I would have said, "Please, can I be president?"
结果这成了我生命中最寂寞的12个月
And then it turned out to be the 12 loneliest months of my life.
我姨妈以前经常这样谈起寂寞
My auntie used to talk about loneliness like that.
- 好吧 - 对
- Okay, so, right, you know that. - Yeah, yeah.
我们曾经非常 非常亲近
We were pretty, pretty close,
特别是因为我妈妈太老了
especially 'cause my mother was so much older.
事实上 她老到足够当我祖母了
Old enough to be my grandmother, as a matter of fact.
- 对 - 对
- Yeah. - Yeah.
也许我姨妈是我亲妈
Maybe my auntie was actually my real mother
而我妈其实是我祖母
and my mother was actually my grandmother.
哇 这样合理多了
wow, that's starting to make a whole lot of sense.
除了我 大家都知道
Everybody knew about it but me, too.
这是要祈祷吗 女士
Are we praying, ma'am?
不 我只是要躺下
No, I'm just gonna lie down.
天啊
Oh, God.
我赢了就好了
I wish I had won.
我希望大家都赢
I wish everybody won.
女士?
Ma'am?
女士? 好吧
Ma'am? Okay.
你能留下吗
Can you just stay?
当然 女士
Absolutely, ma'am.
就职典礼日
上午 7:39
特别的果昔
Special smoothie
给特别的你
for a special lady.
- 发生了什么 - 我不知道
- What happened? - I don't know.
天啊 我没操理查德吧
Oh, my God, I hope I didn't fuck Richard.
什么
What?
- 需要帮忙吗 - 不
- Okay, you need some help? - No.
蒙特兹太太和她的家人在路上了
Okay, Mrs. Montez and her family, they're on their way.
你要在北门廊门口迎接他们
You're gonna greet them at the North Portico doorway.
妈妈
Mom.
你见我的影片了吗 硬盘丢了
Have you seen my film? The hard drive is missing.
亲爱的 看看你
Honey, look at you.
是啊 我一直在为拯救农场做宣传
Yeah, I've been working with this new stylist
所以请了个新的造型师
since I've been doing all this press for the rescue farm.
这是我的新形象
It's my new look.
妈妈 你会打理你的头发的 对吧
Mom, you're gonna do something with your hair, right?
天啊 看看这个
Oh, God. Look at this.
好了 你听我说 听我说
Okay, you listen to me. Listen to me.
他们可以夺走你的总统之位
They can take away your presidency,
你的权力 你的尊严
they can take away your power, they can take away your dignity,
但有一样他们夺不走的是什么
but what is the one thing that they cannot take away from you?
- 我的美 - 这就对了 我们走吧
- My beauty. - That's right. Let's go.
走后门 后门
Go back door! Back door!
举起来
Put it up!
- 就这样 - 你犯规
- That's it. - You fouled me.
你们知道整个该死的雷伯恩议会大厦
Do you realize the whole goddamn Rayburn House Office Building
都能听到你和你的废柴军团
can hear you and your twink
在这儿互插食道吗
army in here cock scraping each other's esophagi?
好的 先生 抱歉 先生 我们是在打闹
Yes, sir. Sorry, sir. We were roughhousing.
天啊 威尔 你看到的也如我所见吗
Jesus, Will, are you looking at what I'm looking at here?
威尔 告诉他招聘男性员工的第一条法则
Will, tell him the first rule of hiring male staff.
他们魅力必须比议员少很多
They must be substantially less attractive than the congressman.
我差点雇了一个伊拉克老兵
And I almost hired an Iraqi war veteran.
半边脸三度烧伤
Third degree burns on half of his face,
不过他性格好 所以...
but the guy had personality, so...
威尔 告诉他为什么我雇了你
Will, tell him why I hired you instead.
因为我的外表和礼仪都招人烦
Because I'm repulsive both in appearance and manner.
在你像拉拉队长要堕的胎一样
Now let me give you some advice
被拽出去之前
before you're yanked out
我来给你些建议
of here like a cheerleader's unwanted fetus.
谨言慎行
You say nothing and you do less.
摘掉这个破眼睛
And take off those fucking glasses.
你看起来像克里斯托弗·里夫[超人扮演者]
You look like Clark Kent if they
被挖出来的尸体扮演的克拉克·肯特[超人]
dug up Christopher Reeve's corpse to play the part.
至于你们 各位女士 这里是华盛顿 不是迈阿密
And as for you ladies, this is DC, not Miami.
- 恭喜 乔纳 - 谢了
- Congratulations, Jonah. - Thanks, man.
操他大爷
Fuck that guy.
来啊 游戏开始 我们继续
Come on, let's go. Game on. Here we go.
- 好吗 预备 - 空中传球
- All right, ready? - Alley-oop!
我的蛋
My fucking nuts!
擦 柯尔特
shit, Colt.
叫个医生 打给我妈
Call a doctor and call my mom.
嘿 你用过那个杜鲁门保龄球馆吗
Hey, have you ever used that Truman bowling alley?
不 当然没有 我在这工作
No, no, of course not. I worked here.
我来白宫又不是为了庆祝四年级生日派对
I didn't go to the White House for a fourth grade birthday party.
天啊 抱歉
Jesus. I'm sorry.
抱歉 那是
I'm sorry. That's
- 艾米 嗨 - 嗨 凯蒂
- Amy, hi. - Hey, Candi.
恭喜 蒙特兹的新幕僚长
Congratulations. Montez's new chief of staff.
- 本只是带我转转 - 是的
- Ben here is just showing me around. - I am.
你来这里面试了太多次
You've interviewed here so many times,
我还以为你早对这里
I'd think that you'd know
了如指掌了呢
the place like the back of your hand by now.
- 肯特·戴维森 - 迈克·麦克林托克
- Kent Davison. - Mike McLintock.
新工作找得怎么样了
Any luck with the new job search?
没关系 我回到了《每日邮报》工作 所以我们还行
Oh, it's all right. I'm back at the "Post," So we're good. Yeah.
这位是黛博拉莉 我们的代孕妈妈
This is Debralee, our surrogate.
- 你好 - 双胞胎在肚子里
- Hi. - The twins are in there.
- 肚子里 - 是的
- In there. - In here.
这位是艾伦
And this is Ellen,
我的新女儿 她3岁了
our new big girl. She's three.
麦克 她的头围看上去已经六岁了
Mike, she has the head circumference of a six-year-old.
我六岁
I'm six.
她说什么?
What did she say?
很有趣的事
Here's an interesting fact.
你知道这间屋在被涂红之前
Would you believe that it was called the Red Room
就被称作红屋了么？
before it was actually painted red?
我听说了
I heard that.
那时候刷这个屋要多少钱
What'd it cost to paint this thing back then?
- 12美元 - 12美元 我还以为15美元呢
- $12. - Yeah, $12. I was thinking right around 15.
当时还是奴隶制 所以可能不要钱
I think it was a slave state, so it might have been free.
我刚在想... 孩子们
Oh, I'm just wondering... boys.
- 孩子们 不要管他们 - 我儿子们像他们这么大的时候
- Boys. They're fine. - Hell, when my boys were that age,
能把这拆了
they'd have just torn this place apart.
我有三个儿子 我家闻上去就像是腋窝的味道
I have three boys. My entire house smells like an armpit.
真好我家是女儿
Ooh, hate to hear that. See, glad I have girls.
女孩们后来会让你更费心
Girls will cost you later.
女孩最不好了
Mm, girls are the worst.
我听说今晚气温要降到20度以下呢[-6.7摄氏度]
Well, I also heard that it might go down into the teens tonight.
为了舞会我得把皮草准备好吧
Hey, I better get out my fur for the ball tonight, right?
对啊
Yes, you should.
我恨不得每天都热
Well, give me the heat any day.
不过再说了 我是墨西哥长大的
But then again, I grew up in Mexico.
当然 我们知道
Well, sure, yeah, we know that.
他家是哈利斯科州的
His family is from Jalisco.
那热死了[西语]
Es muy caliente there.
劳拉 你又是来自俄亥俄州哪里的呢?[揭劳拉实为美国乡下人]
And where exactly in Ohio are you from, Laura?
我家
Um, well, I grew up
正好在克利夫兰旁边 但是
right outside of Cleveland, but after, you know,
15年过去了 我觉得自己就是个土生土长的新墨西哥人
15 years, I feel like I am 100% New Mexican.
新墨西哥 而不是墨西哥?
New Mexican, but not Mexican?
在所有白宫的传统中
Of all the White House traditions,
这一个应该是我最喜欢的
this one is probably my favorite.
- 是吗 - 是的
- Is it? Oh. - Yeah.
该死 刚才还有啊
Damn it. I just had it.
我每天都带着 但是现在我找不到了
I have this thing every day and now I can't find it.
好
Okay.
约100万人正在焦急的等待
An estimated one million people are anxiously awaiting
劳拉 蒙特兹总统就职典礼
新任总统劳拉·蒙特兹的到来
the arrival of President-Elect Laura Montez.
近两百万支持者出席就职典礼
蒙特兹！蒙特兹！蒙特兹！
Montez! Montez! Montez!
女士们 先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
美国总统赛琳娜·梅耶
the President of the United States, Selina Meyer.
即将离职的赛琳娜 梅耶总统抵达就职典礼
当选总统蒙特兹抵达
已经下了楼梯
President Meyer has taken the stage.
她在与一位十分迷人的不明女子打招呼
And she's greeting a very attractive stranger.
那是她的女儿凯瑟琳·梅耶
That is first daughter Catherine Meyer.
可惜
Oh, wow. Too bad.
权力交接仪式正式开始
The handoff of power has begun.
当选总统蒙特兹将进行宣誓
President-Elect Montez will be sworn in
并首次以总统的身份进行全国性发言
and address the nation as president for the first time.
为什么 安德鲁?
Why'd you do it, Andrew?
我许诺了你国务卿啊
I offered you secretary of state.
你给每个人都许诺了
You offered it to everybody in town.
你的头塞在蒙特兹屁股里那么深
Your head is so far up Montez's ass.
下一次亚力山卓过生日
Next time it's Alejandro's birthday,
他就能直接射你一脸了
he's gonna come all over your face.
是真的
That's the truth.
梅耶总统
President Meyer taking a
正在和她的副总统 同时也是
moment to catch up with her vice president
一直以来的政治盟友安德鲁·道尔谈话
and longtime political ally Andrew Doyle.
他们两的关系非常特别
Those two have a very special relationship.
我 劳拉·普莉希拉·蒙特兹 庄严地宣誓...
I, Laura Priscilla Montez, do solemnly swear...
劳拉 蒙特兹总统就职宣誓
我 劳拉·普莉希拉·蒙特兹 庄严地宣誓...
I, Laura Priscilla Montez, do solemnly swear...
...我将忠诚有效地行使
...that I will faithfully execute the office
美国总统职权...
of President of the United States...
...我将忠诚有效地行使
...that I will faithfully execute the office
美国总统职权…
of President of the United States...
...尽最大努力
...and will to the best of my ability...
...保障 保护
...preserve, protect,
保卫美国宪法
and defend the Constitution of the United States.
...保障 保护
...preserve, protect,
保卫美国宪法
and defend the Constitution of the United States.
上帝为证
So help me God.
祝贺你 总统女士
Congratulations, Madam President.
谢谢[西语]
Gracias.
劳拉 蒙特兹总统发表就职演讲
亲爱的民众们
My fellow citizens,
这是一个新时代的开启
this is the dawn of a new era.
一个新时代[西语]
Una epoca nueva.
婴儿喇嘛获救 蒙特兹总统解放西藏
我们中断蒙特兹的演讲
We are interrupting President Montez's speech
为您播报突发新闻
to bring you breaking news.
在您的屏幕左侧
On the left side of your screen,
是安德鲁空军基地的实时画面
you're seeing live footage from Andrews Air Force Base.
我们刚刚得知在蒙特兹总统上任后仅数分钟
We have just learned that mere minutes into her presidency,
她就和中国政府
President Montez has brokered a deal
就解放西藏问题上达成了协议
with the Chinese government to free Tibet.
乘坐飞机的是小喇嘛
And on board that plane are the so-called baby lamas,
被中国政府关押几十年的
Tibetan spiritual leaders who have been freed
藏族领袖终于被释放
from decades of Chinese captivity
这也是这份历史性合约中的一部分条款
as part of this historic agreement.
这无疑将给蒙特兹总统
This will no doubt put
获得诺贝尔奖和平奖的机会
President Montez in line for the Nobel Prize.
...我们所有的问题 我们要相信...
...all of our problems. We must put our faith...
你可能不相信 但是她刚刚让喇嘛自由了
You're not gonna believe this, but she just freed the lamas.
什么？
What?
她跟中国谈成了 解放西藏
She brokered with the Chinese to free Tibet.
谢谢 上帝保佑你们
Thank you. May God bless you
上帝保佑美国
and may God bless America.
总统女士
Madam President.
詹姆斯议员
Oh, Senator James.
对于女性来说历史性的一天
An historic day for womankind.
你觉得演讲如何?
What'd you think of the speech?
我不知道她的胸部那么大
I had no idea her tits were that big.
所以你接下来什么打算?
So what's next for you?
我一直希望可以生活在一个小城镇
Well, I've always dreamed of living in a small town,
在大街上有一处小地方
having a little place on Main Street,
在外面立一个小牌子
hanging a shingle out front,
经营一个属于自己的数百万的对冲基金
and running my own little multibillion-dollar hedge fund.
你懂 重回基础
You know, back to basics.
好的 再见了
Okay. All right. Well, I'll see you around.
- 再见 - 再见
- See you around. - See you around.
- 总统女士 - 什么?
- Madam President. - What?
鞋不错
Nice shoes.
拜托
Oh, come on, man.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
- 苏在哪? - 不知道
- Where's Sue? - I don't know.
我不擅长告别
Well, I'm not good with good-byes.
也不擅长赢取竞选
Or winning presidential elections.
才不是
Well, that's not true.
- 是的 - 好的
- Yeah, it is. - Okay.
嗯...
Um...
我无语了
I don't know what to say.
我该写点什么吗 女士?
Was I supposed to write something, ma'am?
没人告诉我啊
Nobody told me.
我以为他要领养个婴儿
I thought he was getting a baby.
那可不是婴儿
Yeah, that's not a baby.
我们给美国贡献了一切
Uh, well, we gave America everything we had.
是啊
Yeah, sure did.
激励人心 女士 一路顺风
Inspiring words, ma'am. Godspeed.
谢谢 所有人
Thank you, all of you.
这...
It's...
好了 姑娘们 走了
All right, let's go, girls.
- 上去吧 - 再见 女士
- Get on the thing. - Good-bye, ma'am.
- 女士 - 再见
- Ma'am. - Bye.
女士!
Ma'am!
女士 我只想谢谢你
Ma'am, I just want to thank you
- 你所做的一切 - 艾米 跟我们一起走
- for everything you did - Amy, just come with us.
- 不 - 不 你来吧
- No. - No, no, you should just come.
好吧 但我东西还没...
Okay, but I don't even have my...
他们去哪?
Where are they going?
天呐 从远处看 还真的是漂亮
Gosh, from a distance, it looks really beautiful.
对 从远处看
Yeah, from a distance.
谁的手机能借我用一下?  我需要联系一下巴迪
Can I borrow somebody's phone? I have to check on Buddy.
- 你养狗了? - 巴迪是...
- Oh, did you get a dog? - Buddy's my...
怎么了?
Ooh, what was that?
- 好吧 - 什么鬼东西?
- Okay. - What the fuck is that?
一个引擎出了点小问题 总统女士
Small problem with one of the engines, Madam President.
- 我们要返航了 - 天呐
- We're gonna have to take her back down. - Oh, Lord.
真是个没油的好时机
Hell of a time to run out of gas.
如果你走得离飞机远一点
If you could just step away from the aircraft for a bit,
我们可以给你安排车队
we'll call you a motorcade.
天呐
Oh, my God.
- 我踩在什么东西上? - 草 女士
- What am I walking on? - Grass, ma'am.
- 妈 - 怎么了?
- Mom. - What?
你确定你不知道我电影的硬盘在哪里吗?
Are you sure you don't know where the hard drive of my film is?
- 不知道 - 不知道
- No. - No.
什么声音?
What is that sound?
游行 女士
The parade, ma'am.
我可以从这里走回去
I think I can walk back from here.
天呐
Oh, my God.
这里
Here you go.
说不定这可以毁了她的游行
Maybe it'll ruin her parade.
以上来自于国家广场 转接给你沃夫
That's it from the National Mall. Back to you, Wolf.
直播结束
And clear.
- 干的漂亮 伊根 - 谢谢
- Nice work, Egan. - Thank you.
- 我有一个全职工作给你 - 真的?
- I may have a full-time gig for you. - Really?
我们有一个
We've got an opening for someone
夜间报道国务院的机会
to cover the state department on the overnight.
- 真的? - 别小题大做 克朗凯特[美越战时期著名记者]
- Really? - Easy, Cronkite.
- 你的黑夜换个地方就是白天了嘛 凯瑞? - 怎么了?
- Just think of it as morning somewhere. Carrie? - Yes?
能把明天的背景调查给我吗?
Could you give me tomorrow's research, please?
所以 你怎么想
So, what do you say?
我刚刚收到CBS的工作
I just got an offer from CBS News.
格雷格 我想说...
So, Greg, I will say this--
伊根退场
Egan out.
我收到你的邮件了
Yeah, I just got your email.
我只是想确认那个工作是CBS的吧?
I just want to make sure the job is with CBS, right?
哥伦比亚广播电台?
That's Columbia Broadcasting?
只是一些局部的小肿胀  瑞安先生
Yeah, there's just some minor swelling, Mr. Ryan,
一点冰敷就可以了
but nothing a little ice won't fix.
太好了
Excellent.
我有明晚就职舞会的门票
Hoo. I have tickets to the inaugural ball tonight.
我是议员
Yeah. I'm a congressman.
第二张票还没人 如果你想去的话
The second ticket is unclaimed if you're available.
我结婚了 我的戒指在手套下面
I'm married. I have the ring hiding under the gloves.
我看见了
No, I saw it.
我也只能直说了
Anyway, there is no easy way to say this,
你左边的蛋蛋上有一个肿块
but you have a lump on your left testicle.
我要做一个活体切片检查 然后我们可以取出来
I just want to biopsy it and we can take it from there.
取什么从哪取?
Take what from where?
早期的监测可以预防
Early detection would have prevented this.
我们非常鼓励定期的自我检查
We really encourage regular self-exams.
懂了
Yeah, I know.
他们在罗斯福厅等你
Oh, they're waiting for you in the Roosevelt Room, ma'am.
- 谢谢 苏 - 不用
- Thank you, Sue. - Of course.
塞琳娜 好消息 我们找到了内华达丢失的选票
Selina, good news. We found the missing Nevada ballots.
你赢了
You won.